[Music]
[音乐]
我将向您展示如何制作
I'm going to show you how to make a
坐狗弹出，这很有趣
锐角v形折叠的使用方式
I'm going to show you how to make a
sitting dog pop up which is just a fun
这个可爱的角度V型折
不常使用的异常机制
sitting dog pop up which is just a fun
way of using the acute angle v-folds
但这是一种很好的使用方式
所以这是我已经有了的基本表
way of using the acute angle v-folds
this cute angle v-fold is quite an
折叠它，我再给它多一点
折叠我们要用一张像
this cute angle v-fold is quite an
unusual mechanism not used very often
将其对折并真正弄皱
好，我已经开始制作一个
unusual mechanism not used very often
but this is quite a nice way of using it
我要去的阶段是
这是原始表的放置方式
but this is quite a nice way of using it
so here's the base sheet I've already
这是原始表
折痕，我们提出了一个折痕
so here's the base sheet I've already
folded it I'll just give it a bit more
从那个角大约45度
确实取决于您想要的角度
folded it I'll just give it a bit more
folding we're gonna use a sheet like
你的狗坐在那折叠的地方
回到您看到的这是折痕
folding we're gonna use a sheet like
this fold it in half and creased really
所以在底部有标签
剪掉标签剪掉标签
this fold it in half and creased really
well and I already started making one so
一分钟后再整理一下
也想把狗的前面
well and I already started making one so
the stage I'd got to is this is the
来这里，我就剪
在那儿笔直地画
the stage I'd got to is this is the
original sheet here's how it fits onto
坐在狗上面，所以我们有后面
像这样的腿和来
original sheet here's how it fits onto
the original sheet here's the first
前进，所以它们是选项卡的一部分，我们
像这样把狗的胸部抬起来
the original sheet here's the first
crease and we put a crease coming up
这些前腿像
那里
crease and we put a crease coming up
from that corner at roughly 45 degrees
从那里没有办法切掉那些
我已经这样做了，这很好
from that corner at roughly 45 degrees
depending really on what angle you want
这是我的画这是我做的
这些是他们要折叠的标签
depending really on what angle you want
your dog's sitting at like that folded
在下面还是外面
看看它是怎么回事
your dog's sitting at like that folded
back as you can see this is the crease
像这样的页面可能有
前爪向内，后爪向外
back as you can see this is the crease
so there's tabs along the bottom we've
我在后面也做了一点缝
在这里，所以我们可以在我也适合尾巴
so there's tabs along the bottom we've
cut tabs off cut the tabs off here we'll
要把最上面的变成一对
的标签，所以我们可以坚持下去
cut tabs off cut the tabs off here we'll
sort that out some more in a minute we
弯下腰把你打开
顶部的两个标签，然后我们开始
sort that out some more in a minute we
also want the front of the dog to be
坚持下去，我们现在
把狗放到页面上，看看
also want the front of the dog to be
coming down here so I'll just cut
你知道你想要他什么角度
在你想要他们真的很宽的时候，我想
coming down here so I'll just cut
straight up there you can draw your
最好窄一点
我可能实际上把尾巴放在前面
straight up there you can draw your
sitting dog onto it so we have the back
我们走得更远，所以我将
卷曲的尾巴卷曲一点
sitting dog onto it so we have the back
legs as sort of like this and coming
浓密的苏联狡猾也许
在一侧放一点胶水
legs as sort of like this and coming
forward so they're part of the tab we
在里面，所以它关闭
现在我们将两条后腿粘上
forward so they're part of the tab we
have the dog's chest coming up like this
这个版本我把它们缩小了一点
这么大的狗，我们只做一个
have the dog's chest coming up like this
and these front legs coming down like
一边，然后我们将其折叠下来
我们会做另一个，尽管他会
and these front legs coming down like
there
这样的东西，所以有一条腿
现在关上它，放一点胶
there
and from there no can cut those out
另一边应该做了
当我在前脚时，但在这里我们
and from there no can cut those out
which is well I've already done so
请关闭此按钮，对不起，我做了一个
这个尾巴的错误，这只是一个
which is well I've already done so
here's my drawing here's what I've done
坏角度
将其移到我们现在可以关闭
here's my drawing here's what I've done
these are the tabs they're going to fold
他坐下来这脚
还没粘好我最好放些胶
these are the tabs they're going to fold
in underneath or outside let's have a
在这方面，我当然做得更好
指向我有一个指向
in underneath or outside let's have a
look how it's it's going to sit on the
我要把另外一个指向
[掌声]
look how it's it's going to sit on the
page like this like that probably have
我把它粘在适当的地方
还是柔软的，所以我将其关闭
page like this like that probably have
the front paws in and the back paws out
如果需要移动它仍然可以移动
那就是我们的基本狗
the front paws in and the back paws out
I've also made a little slit at the back
现在我们需要一个头，像一个
这些审判只是一个不错的
I've also made a little slit at the back
here so we can fit a tail in I'm also
卡的三角形位看起来像
可能是一个很好的狗头
here so we can fit a tail in I'm also
going to make the very top into a couple
像这样的东西看看看起来
像所有标签一样
going to make the very top into a couple
of tabs so we can stick a head on there
那还不错，也许太大
是的，那真的可以
of tabs so we can stick a head on there
bend those over you open it up there's
我可能再拍几副，所以我
也可以戴上双耳
bend those over you open it up there's
the two tabs at the top then we're going
弯腰弯腰，然后弯腰
现在我要逐只狗
the two tabs at the top then we're going
to stick the head on with now we'll
头上各放一点胶
一边滑动一边柔软
to stick the head on with now we'll
stick the dog down on the page just see
看看你认为有什么好处
向下倾斜一点，向上倾斜一点
stick the dog down on the page just see
you know what sort of angle you want him
很喜欢它看到它是如何工作的
虽然耳朵和耳朵似乎还可以
you know what sort of angle you want him
at you want them really wide I think
再次，我只是让他们很松散
看起来像这样的耳朵
at you want them really wide I think
pretty narrow is best
而且应该能够像
继续前进
pretty narrow is best
I might actually put the tail in before
留在奥利维亚
一个简单的弹出窗口，很容易制作
I might actually put the tail in before
we go any further so I'll just cut a
尖头v形折叠的很好用
如果您愿意，可以随时强调
we go any further so I'll just cut a
nice curly tail curling up a little bit
狗，你可以知道戴上帽子吗
它，但它的夹克袜子你知道
nice curly tail curling up a little bit
bushy Soviet foxy maybe
随便玩也可以
装饰和它的基础上坐
put a bit of glue on one side and put it
这样就很好了，简单的弹出式窗口
[音乐]
put a bit of glue on one side and put it
in there so it shuts up
[掌声]
您
now we glue the two back legs maybe on
[音乐]